mydala.com 2014-12-16

# mydala | privacy

This Privacy Policy relates solely to the information collection and use practices of our web site located at [http://www.mydala.com](http://www.mydala.com/) (this "Website"), and any individual websites or merchant-specific, city-specific, or state-specific websites now or hereinafter contained within or otherwise available through external hyperlinks with our Website (the "Minisites"). We ("Kinobeo Software Private Limited" or "Kinobeo") recognize that many visitors and users of this Website and/or the Minisites ("User(s)") are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time, has been developed to address those concerns. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy, and become familiar with it.

Your use of this Website indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What type of information is collected by us?**

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

**Personally Identifiable Information.**

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is information that identifies a specific end user. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, ordering a product or service from the Institutions (as defined in Terms of Use), submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, entering a promotion sponsored by the Institution, filling out a survey, posting a review, sending feedback to us or the Institutions, requesting information about our services, applying for a job or posting a video (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, cell number, telephone number and date of birth. When you order products or services, we may also ask you to provide us with financial information, including but not limited to, your credit card or debit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity. We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you, administer promotions, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with the Institutions. For instance, if you send our customer service an email we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. In addition, if you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of any recipient. We may use that other person's contact information to allow him or her to view and accept your gift or to allow the recipient to access the information you requested we send. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use, and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. 

In the event there is any change in your Personally Identifiable Information like your address, phone number or email ID, you may send us intimation about the changes and we will make the necessary amendment in our records.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**

Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("NPII") is information that does not identify a specific end user. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We, and/or our authorized third party service providers that perform function on our behalf like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails ("Third Party Service Providers") and authorized third party advertisers that provide advertising services to Kinobeo ("Third Party Advertisers"), may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with Third Party Service Providers and Third Party Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming. 

**When and how do we collect the information?**

We collect information from you for various purposes including but not limited to the following: 

**Member Registration**

If you choose to become a registered member of this Website, you must provide your name, address, telephone or cell phone number, e-mail address, a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including but not limited to the following: 

  * Personal identification purposes
  * Completing purchases
  * Allowing us to contact you for customer service purposes
  * If necessary, customizing the content of this Website to strive to meet your specific needs
  * For making product or other improvements to our site

In addition, we need your e-mail address to confirm your new member registration and each transaction you conduct on our site. As a registered member of this Website, you will be entitled to savings and benefits on deals including, but not limited to restaurants, hotels, holiday packages, etc. You could, in addition, look forward to receiving by e-mail monthly newsletters, daily promotions offering special deals, updates for new services, and other noteworthy items. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types of e-mail messages. Please see our Opt-Out Policy described below for details.

**Member Profile**

As a registered member of this Website, you can choose to complete your online profile by providing us with personal preferences, credit card billing information, and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist you in making reservations quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly. For example, you can store your credit card billing information so that when you make a transaction, we may automatically pre-fill the credit card billing information for you.

**Online Surveys**

We value opinions and comments from members, so we frequently conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated, and used to make improvements to our Website and its services and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for our Website members. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.

**Promotions**

We may sponsor promotions to give our Website members the opportunity to win prizes. Information collected by us for such activities may include contact information and survey questions. We use contact information to notify the winners and survey information to develop promotions and product improvements to our Website.

**Automatic Logging of Session Data**

We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our Website. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the site, how long visitors to the site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is very common on the Internet and our Website's use of cookies is similar to that of other reputable online companies.

There are many myths circulating about cookies, but you should know that cookies are usually only read by the server that placed them. We confirm that our cookies are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses or harvest your personal information and that our cookies are not intended to be used for such purposes, as explained below.

Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our Website. Our Website uses cookies to personalize your experience on the site, and with respect to advertisements. As to the former, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type your log - in name each time (only your password is needed). We may also use such cookies to display an advertisement to you while you are on the Website.

A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our Website and no PII is gathered from you by the use of these cookies, nor is this information shared with any third party. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our Third Party Advertisers. These entities may use aggregated statistics about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about travel - related goods and services that you may be interested in. The information they collect does not include your PII.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. Our Website supports your right to block any unwanted internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking our Website cookies may disable certain features on the Website, and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the Website. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from sites you trust, like our Website.

**Access by Third Party Advertisers**

The Third Party Advertisers may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. Any such information is anonymous. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. No PII is collected during this process. The information is anonymous, and does not link online actions to an identifiable person.

**Personalized Services**

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the Website. To the extent these services are provided, and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making the site the better and easier to use.

**Compliance with law**

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose our Website member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Kinobeo or any or all of its subsidiaries and associates, and its employees, directors or officers, or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if Kinobeo or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition.

Apart from the above, we may collect information from you for providing our complete range of services like issuing vouchers for products and/or services, maintaining discussion forums, interacting with Website Users for customer feedback and resolving customer queries and issues, processing requests for signing up for special offers and maintenance of Website.

**When and to whom do we release Personally Identifiable Information?**

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

**We may share your information with Institutions.** We issue vouchers for products or services to be provided by Institutions (both restaurant and non-restaurant merchants with whom we have an association for providing you with value deals at discounted price). We share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with Institutions in order to help them provide you with better service and track the value of our program. Sharing this information will allow an Institution to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with an Institution if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the Institution involved in that Identification Activity. For example, if you purchase a promotional voucher for a particular restaurant, we may share your name, email address, cell phone number, telephone and city with that restaurant.

**We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** We provide some of our services through third parties. These "Third Party Service Providers? perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails and sms. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with Third Party Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send post, sms or email, administer promotions, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and entities with whom we have business relationships ("Business Associates?) and may have to also share their information with Third Party Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a service, we release your financial (credit card, debit card, net banking, mobile payment, etc) information to the card-issuing bank/provider to confirm payment for the service and, if applicable, release your address to the delivery service to deliver the service. We encourage Institutions and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.

**We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others.** We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

**When and to whom we release Non-Personally Identifiable Information?**

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Institutions, Business Associates and Third Party Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with Third Party Advertisers and other parties as provided below: We may use Third Party Advertisers to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable Information usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Third Party Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

**What is our Opt-Out policy?**

At any time, you may unsubscribe from our "Daily Deal" email or sms or other newsletter or similar services through the "My Account" link on our Website's home page. As a member, you will occasionally receive e-mail updates from us about special offers, new services, and other noteworthy items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each email message or send us an email to [unsubscribe@mydala.com.](mailto:unsubscribe@mydala.com.) We reserve the right to limit membership to those who will accept such emails. Members will be notified via email prior to any actions taken.

###### What security measures are available on the Website?

**Data Security**

We take reasonable steps to maintain the security of the Personally Identifiable Information that we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as installing electronic security systems that guard against unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk.

**Payment Security**

All payments on our Website are VeriSign SSL secured. This means all personal information you provide on the Website is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. The same process is replicated when you make purchases on our Website.

**Disclaimer**

Our Website contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another web site for which we have no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, and your Website membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 15, 2009. Any material changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices via email to privacy@mydala.com. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. We will attempt to respond to all of your reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt of your email. Thank you for using mydala.com!
